<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Socialist Legacy</title>
    <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Socialist Legacy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 19:56:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://socialistlegacy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The true realm of freedom</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/thetruerealmoffreedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 19:56:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/thetruerealmoffreedom/</guid>
      <description>We have seen that the capitalist process of production is a historically determined form of the social process of production in general. The latter is as much a production process of material conditions of human life as a process taking place under specific historical and economic production relations, producing and reproducing these production relations themselves, and thereby also the bearers of this process, their material conditions of existence and their mutual relations, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A common plan</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/acommonplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 17:58:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/acommonplan/</guid>
      <description>What will this new social order have to be like?
Above all, it will have to take the control of industry and of all branches of production out of the hands of mutually competing individuals, and instead institute a system in which all these branches of production are operated by society as a whole – that is, for the common account, according to a common plan, and with the participation of all members of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droit au travail</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/droitautravail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 17:14:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/droitautravail/</guid>
      <description>The first draft of the constitution, made before the June days, still contained the droit au travail, the right to work, the first clumsy formula wherein the revolutionary demands of the proletariat are summarized. It was transformed into the droit à l’assistance, the right to public relief, and what modern state does not feed its paupers in some form or other? The right to work is, in the bourgeois sense, an absurdity, a miserable, pious wish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not malign</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/notmalign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 17:10:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/notmalign/</guid>
      <description>He who is not malign does not live serenely but with a peculiarly chaste hardness and intolerance. Lacking appropriate objects, his love can scarcely express itself except by hatred for the inappropriate, in which admittedly he comes to resemble what he hates. The bourgeois, however, is tolerant. His love of people as they are stems from his hatred of what they might be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Posterity</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/toposterity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/toposterity/</guid>
      <description>Indeed I live in the dark ages!A guileless word is an absurdity. A smooth forehead betokensA hard heart. He who laughsHas not yet heardThe terrible tidings.
Ah, what an age it isWhen to speak of trees is almost a crimeFor it is a kind of silence about injustice!And he who walks calmly across the street,Is he not out of reach of his friendsIn trouble?
It is true: I earn my livingBut, believe me, it is only an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Reflections of the socialist legacy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://socialistlegacy.com/epigraphia/test/</guid>
      <description>Test</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>